Emmanuel Bernal Velázquez

Frontend Developer

<u>LinkedIn</u> - <u>Behance</u> - <u>Github</u> - <u>Codepen</u> - <u>Email</u> - Tel. 7224040741 Calimaya, Mexico

I'm a Frontend Developer and UI Designer specializing in web application development using JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, HTML, and CSS. I am passionate about programming and known for my creativity, punctuality, and responsibility. I excel in collaborative team environments and consistently demonstrate my commitment to achieving goals and overcoming challenges.

I have a personal project called "TheFrontdev," which is dedicated to sharing knowledge and continuous learning within the development community through Instagram and Twitch.

Work Experience

Frontend Developer

Anzen Digital
Mexico City, Mexico.
November 2019 to date.

Activities:

- Develop web applications from scratch and proofs of concept with JavaScript using Angular, consuming REST APIs, working in conjunction with the UI/UX design team.
- Manage organizational Github account.
- Implement in some projects the continuous integration with AWS Amplify.
- Support banking application with Stencil.js, Angular, HTML, CSS as technology
- Work under agile methodologies (SCRUM, Kanban).

Web Developer

Desarrollo Industrial RISORSE Toluca, Mexico. May2019 a Octuber 2019

Activities::

- Develop web applications with PHP using Laravel, JavaScript and MySQL.
- Develop desktop applications using C++ and SQL Server.

Web Developer

SatSys Calimaya, Mexico. Octubre 2018 a Abril de 2019

Actividades:

 Develop web applications with PHP using Symphony, Drupal CMS, JavaScript and MySQL.

Web Developer Jr

Bit Technologies Mexico Toluca, Mexico. July 2016 a June 2018

Actividades:

- Web application development with PHP using Laravel, JavaScript and MySQL.
- Customer support.

Education

Computer Systems Engineering

Tecnológico de Estudios Superiores de Tianguistenco 2015 - 2018

Idiomas

- Español: nativo.
- Inglés: básico intermedio.

Certifications

Diseño UX/UI

CoderHouse Julio 2022

Marketing Digital: Community
 Manager & Publicidad

CoderHouse Marzo 2023

Technology Stack

- Angular
- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Git

- Figma
- CorelDraw
- MySQL
- PHP